{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb26"
	},
	"question": "What tag would be used to link to a seperate HTML file?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"\u003ca\u003e",
		"\u003clink\u003e",
		"\u003cem\u003e",
		"\u003ccite\u003e"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "\u003ca\u003e",
	"language": "html",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb27"
	},
	"question": "What does the 'ol' tag stand for?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"On License",
		"Over Layout",
		"Unordered List",
		"None of the above"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "None of the above",
	"language": "html",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb28"
	},
	"question": "What tag is used to create a supplemented number/letter?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"\u003cstrong\u003e",
		"\u003csup\u003e",
		"\u003cem\u003e",
		"\u003csub\u003e"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "\u003csup\u003e",
	"language": "html",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb29"
	},
	"question": "Which tag creates the biggest text?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"\u003ch6\u003e",
		"\u003cp\u003e",
		"\u003cem\u003e",
		"\u003ch1\u003e"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "\u003ch1\u003e",
	"language": "html",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2a"
	},
	"question": "What does the 'td' tag stand for?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Top Data",
		"Table Data",
		"Top Date",
		"Table Date"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Table Data",
	"language": "html",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2b"
	},
	"question": "Using CSS, how do you create UPPERCASE text?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"text-transform: uppercase",
		"text-transform: capitalize",
		"text-decoration: uppercase",
		"font-weight: bold"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "text-transform: uppercase",
	"language": "css",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2c"
	},
	"question": "What does the \"0.5\" represent in: background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.5)",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Hue",
		"Opacity",
		"Saturation",
		"Color"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Opacity",
	"language": "css",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2d"
	},
	"question": "Which one would be an example of selecting a direct child element?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"p a {}",
		"li\u003ea {}",
		"h3~p {}",
		"h1+p {}"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "li\u003ea {}",
	"language": "css",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2e"
	},
	"question": "What does CSS stand for?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Cascade Style Sheets",
		"Cascade Size Style",
		"Call Style Shadows",
		"Javascript"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Cascade Style Sheets",
	"language": "css",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb2f"
	},
	"question": "16px is equal to:",
	"allAnswers": [
		"1rem",
		"50%",
		"48pt",
		"1em"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "1em",
	"language": "css",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb30"
	},
	"question": "Looking at document.write('Good Morning'), what does \"Good Morning\" represent?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Method",
		"Member operator",
		"Parameter",
		"Object"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Parameter",
	"language": "javascript",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb31"
	},
	"question": "What layer does Javascript represent in web-development?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Behavior layer",
		"Content layer",
		"Presentation layer",
		"Architectural layer"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Behavior layer",
	"language": "javascript",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb32"
	},
	"question": "At what point does Javascript run?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"When the page loads",
		"Never",
		"After the page loads",
		"The point it is found in the document"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "The point it is found in the document",
	"language": "javascript",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb33"
	},
	"question": "What do the [] brackets represent?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Array",
		"Object",
		"Method",
		"Function"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Array",
	"language": "javascript",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb34"
	},
	"question": "When using Math.ceil, your number will...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Round Down",
		"Round Up",
		"Give Whole Numbers Only",
		"Only Give Two Decimal Places"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Round Up",
	"language": "javascript",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb35"
	},
	"question": "Which method inserts content inside the selected element(s) before the closing tag?",
	"allAnswers": [
		".prepend()",
		".after()",
		".before()",
		".append()"
	],
	"correctAnswer": ".append()",
	"language": "jquery",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb36"
	},
	"question": "How would you hide all of the matched elements of your choice?",
	"allAnswers": [
		".focusout()",
		":hidden Selector",
		".hide()",
		".get()"
	],
	"correctAnswer": ".hide()",
	"language": "jquery",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb37"
	},
	"question": "What does the (\"*\") selector select?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"First Element",
		"Last Child Element",
		"Parent Element",
		"All Elements"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "All Elements",
	"language": "jquery",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb38"
	},
	"question": "What would you use to perform a custom animation of a set of CSS properties?",
	"allAnswers": [
		".playAnimation()",
		".animate()",
		".GIF()",
		".play()"
	],
	"correctAnswer": ".animate()",
	"language": "jquery",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb39"
	},
	"question": "How would you get the value of a computed style property for the first element in the set of matched elements or set one or more CSS properties for every matched element.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"#css(",
		".style()",
		".css()",
		".change()"
	],
	"correctAnswer": ".css()",
	"language": "jquery",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb3a"
	},
	"question": "What tag is used to create a button group?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"\u003crow\u003e",
		"\u003cdiv\u003e",
		"\u003cbutton\u003e",
		"\u003cinput\u003e"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "\u003cdiv\u003e",
	"language": "bootstrap",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb3b"
	},
	"question": "All textual 'input', 'textarea', and 'select' elements with class .form-control have a width of?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"80%",
		"10%",
		"100%",
		"undefined"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "100%",
	"language": "bootstrap",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb3c"
	},
	"question": "A dropdown menu must have a class set of?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"drop dropdown-toggle",
		"drop dropdown",
		"dropdown toggle",
		"dropdown dropdown-toggle"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "dropdown dropdown-toggle",
	"language": "bootstrap",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb3d"
	},
	"question": "What element must be used to create a jumbotron?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"\u003ch1\u003e",
		"\u003cdiv\u003e",
		"\u003ccol\u003e",
		"\u003cjumbotron\u003e"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "\u003cdiv\u003e",
	"language": "bootstrap",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "5fdb534d7c725d24f1e0bb3e"
	},
	"question": "Bootstrap's grid system uses a series of containers, rows, and columns to layout and align content. What class is used before the \"col\" class in this system?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"div",
		"container",
		"col-sm",
		"row"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "row",
	"language": "bootstrap",
	"track": "WDF"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b8252fb2d8bb222c3b867"
	},
	"question": "Node.js was created by...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Facebook in 2010",
		"Ryan Dahl in 2009",
		"Shannon Bradshaw in 2015 ",
		"Microsoft founder Bill Gates in 1998"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Ryan Dahl in 2009",
	"language": "node",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b8288fb2d8bb222c3b868"
	},
	"question": "Express accepts HTTP requests from a client and returns...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"the mongoDB database",
		"a current timestamp",
		"a boolean (true or false)",
		"an HTTP response"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "multiple elements in a render() method",
	"language": "express",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b8289fb2d8bb222c3b869"
	},
	"question": " Express is the __________ of a web application framework",
	"allAnswers": [
		"server-side part",
		"client side part",
		"database part",
		"UI experience"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "server-side part",
	"language": "express",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828afb2d8bb222c3b86a"
	},
	"question": "Express can accept requests from...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"a browser and another server",
		"a mobile device and a desktop application",
		"anything that speaks HTTP",
		"all of the above"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "all of the above",
	"language": "express",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828afb2d8bb222c3b86b"
	},
	"question": "The Express website describes Express as a minimal and flexible Node.js web application framework that provides a robust set of features for web and mobile applications.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "True",
	"language": "express",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828bfb2d8bb222c3b86c"
	},
	"question": "There are hundreds (if not thousands) of community packages that go into an Express application.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "True",
	"language": "express",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828bfb2d8bb222c3b86d"
	},
	"question": "In order to work with React, you must include which two libraries?",
	"allAnswers": [
		"React and ReactDOM",
		"react-redux and react-router-bootstrap",
		"react-scripts and react",
		"none of the above combinations are correct"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "React and ReactDOM",
	"language": "react",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828cfb2d8bb222c3b86e"
	},
	"question": "ReactDOM contains the tools necessary to render React elements in the browser.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "True",
	"language": "react",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828cfb2d8bb222c3b86f"
	},
	"question": "Stateless Functional Components are objects, not functions; therefore, they do have a \"this\" scope",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "False",
	"language": "react",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828cfb2d8bb222c3b870"
	},
	"question": "JSX is __________.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"DOM Control only",
		"Javascript",
		"React-Bootstrap",
		"none of the above"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Javascript",
	"language": "react",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828dfb2d8bb222c3b871"
	},
	"question": "The React.Fragment component lets you return...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"a single element in a render() method",
		"only up to (5) elements in a render() method",
		"elements without using a render() method",
		"multiple elements in a render() method"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "multiple elements in a render() method",
	"language": "react",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828dfb2d8bb222c3b873"
	},
	"question": "Much like Express, the Nodes.js approach to web servers is very minimal.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "True",
	"language": "node",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828efb2d8bb222c3b874"
	},
	"question": "__________ runs at the heart of the MERN Stack by being the software that enables JavaScript to run on the server, uncoupled from a browser, which in turn allows frameworks written in JavaScript (like Express) to be used.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"React",
		"Nodejs",
		"MongoDB",
		"Express"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Nodejs",
	"language": "node",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828efb2d8bb222c3b875"
	},
	"question": "Node simply does not provide the framework for you to build a web server.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "False",
	"language": "node",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828efb2d8bb222c3b876"
	},
	"question": "The Node team has gone to great lengths to make sure the installation process is simple and straightforward on all major platforms",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "True",
	"language": "node",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828ffb2d8bb222c3b877"
	},
	"question": "Select the correct query...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"db.find({\"name\":James}),pretty()",
		"db.find({\"age\":21}).pretty{}",
		"db.find({\"age\":{\"$gte\":21, \"lte\":30}}).pretty()",
		"db.find({\"_id\":3}).count"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "db.find({\"age\":{\"$gte\":21, \"lte\":30}}).pretty()",
	"language": "mongodb",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828ffb2d8bb222c3b878"
	},
	"question": "MongoDB is a relational database.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"True",
		"False"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "False",
	"language": "mongodb",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828ffb2d8bb222c3b879"
	},
	"question": "The greatest benefit of learning to use a database like MongoDB is that:",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Unlike all other existing technologies, MongoDB is free",
		"Using a database will make your app much faster than a pure front-end app",
		"Data doesn’t get erased every time your user refreshes the page",
		"MongoDB will automatically check your code for errors"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Data does not get erased every time your user refreshes the page",
	"language": "mongodb",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604b828ffb2d8bb222c3b87a"
	},
	"question": "MongoDB essentially stores all of its data in _______ format.",
	"allAnswers": [
		"MS Word",
		"GIMP",
		"JSON",
		"LMS"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "JSON",
	"language": "mongodb",
	"track": "MERN"
}
{
	"_id": {
		"$oid": "604bb738fb2d8bb222c3b889"
	},
	"question": "If you try to add data to a MongoDB collection that does not exist, Mongo will...",
	"allAnswers": [
		"Throw an error",
		"Throw an error, close your connection, and shut down your computer",
		"Throw an error and close your connection",
		"Go ahead and create the collection for you"
	],
	"correctAnswer": "Go ahead and create the collection for you",
	"language": "mongodb",
	"track": "MERN"
}
